■
本字幕由
ShinY深影字幕组
原创译制
深影字幕组论坛
http://shinybbs.vip
你总是丢三落四 小姐
You lose everything, my girl.
你已经说了四次了
So you've said four times.
我昨天绝对还戴着它
I definitely had it on yesterday.
你的手套 你的钥匙 还有我为你绣的手帕
Your gloves, your keys, that handkerchief I embroidered for you
■
|
所有东西
Everything!
第五次
Five times.
斯嘉丽小姐
Miss Scarlet?
- 不是 - 是的
- No. - Yes.
我是斯嘉丽小姐
I'm Miss Scarlet.
请问你是丢了什么东西吗
May I inquire if you've lost something?
比如某种珠宝
Some jewellery perhaps?
没错 我母亲的婚戒
Yes, my mother's wedding ring.
你找到它了吗
Have you found it?
你的戒指上刻有文字吗
Does your ring have an inscription?
我父亲给我母亲的 "给我的挚爱 丽维妮娅·斯嘉丽"
From my father to my mother "For my beloved, Livinia Scarlet"
那它就是你的
Then it is yours.
我告诉你很多次了要重新调整尺寸 你看她听了吗
I told you so many times to get it resized, but does she listen?
一位姓波茨的先生昨晚在市停尸房里找到了它
It was found last night in the city mortuary by a Mr Potts.
他是不是说你
Is he the one that calls you
违背基督教教义 像泼妇一样毫无道德
an unChristian woman with the morals of an alley cat.
没错 就是他
Yes, that's the one.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
什么 为什么
What? Why?
罪名是非法闯入市停尸房
For breaking and entering the city mortuary.
去找威灵顿督察
Find Inspector Wellington.
公爵 有人敲门
Duke, the door.
公爵
Duke.
这是你的房子 你去开门
It's your house, you get it.
不好意思打扰你了
Sorry to bother you,
但我想知道威灵顿督察是否在这
but I wondered if Inspector Wellington was there.
有人找你
You've got a visitor.
威灵顿督察
Inspector Wellington!
我需要您的帮助
I need your help.
是伊莱莎
It's Eliza.
她被捕了
She's been arrested.
告诉她我今天休息
Tell her it's my day off.
伊莱莎是谁
Who is this Eliza?
她不是我妻子
She's not my wife.
好了吗 督察
Ready, inspector?
斯嘉丽小姐真的需要您的帮助
Miss Scarlet really does need your help.
翻译  黑猫
翻译  车厘子团子
翻译  明月
翻译  飒白恬
校对&后期  飒白恬
斯嘉丽小姐和公爵
第二季 第三集
这其中肯定是有些误会 菲尔普斯警探
There's clearly been a misunderstanding Detective Phelps.
我并不是想教你做事
Not that I wish to tell you how to do your job.
你是一名经验丰富 备受尊敬的警官
You being an extremely experienced, well regarded officer,
我只是对发生的事感到困惑
I'm simply perplexed as to what has happened.
好吧 让我提示你一下 斯嘉丽小姐
Well, let me enlighten you, Miss Scarlet.
昨晚 有人砸碎了市停尸房的窗户
Last night someone smashed the window of the city mortuary
闯了进去
and broke in.
然后他们进入了里面的办公室
They then gained access to the clerical office inside
偷走了一些高度机密的文件
and stole some highly confidential files.
如果事实如此的话
Well, if that is true
那这真的是既可悲又可耻
then it's both deplorable and a disgrace.
这是停尸房职员波茨先生提供的证词
Words shared by the clerk of the mortuary, Mr Potts,
尽管他更多是在描述你 而非案发情况
although in his case he used to describe you rather than the situation.
我知道这个男人是怎么看我的
I know that man's opinion of me.
"一个无耻的女人
"An unscrupulous woman
西方人经常用snake来形容他们不喜欢的人
她的可信度宛如一袋子的蛇"
who is as trustworthy as a bag of snakes".
事实是 我不是贼
The fact is, I'm no thief.
很高兴你提出了事实 斯嘉丽小姐
So glad you brought up facts, Miss Scarlet,
因为事实提醒着我们
because the fact remains that
你的戒指在犯罪现场被找到了
your ring was found at the crime scene.
我完全不知道它怎么去到那里的
Well, I have no idea how it got there.
女人甚至不被允许进入停尸房
Women aren't even allowed in the mortuary, quite right too.
那不是女士能去的地方
It's no place for a lady.
早上好
Morning to you.
接下来的工作我来接手吧 菲尔普斯警探
I'll take you from here, Detective Phelps.
谢天谢地
Thank God for that.
我很抱歉把你卷入此事 威廉
I'm sorry to have dragged you into this, William.
在我休假的这一天
On my day off.
你在做什么好事吗
Were you doing something nice?
我完全不知道
I have no idea
我母亲的婚戒是怎么跑到犯罪现场的
how my mother's ring found its way to the crime scene.
这确实是一个谜
It's a puzzle indeed.
你觉得我昨天才出生吗
Do you think I was born yesterday?
我警告你 伊莱莎
I'm warning you, Eliza.
下一句从你嘴里说出来的话最好是真的
The next words out of your mouth better be the truth
否则我会亲手把你把你关进牢房
or I'll take you down to the cells myself.
好吧
All right.
我昨天确实去了停尸房
I did go to the mortuary yesterday.
如果波茨先生愿意分享一些基本信息给我的话
I have numerous outstanding cases which I could progress with
我有许多悬案都可以取得进展
if Mr Potts would share some basic information with me.
但他拒绝把我当成专业同行
But he refuses to treat me like a fellow professional.
所以我别无选择 只能像一个普通罪犯一样闯入
So I have no choice but to break in like a common criminal
然后自己查看文件
and check the files myself.
我一定是把我母亲的婚戒丢在了那里
I must have dropped my mother's ring whilst there,
因此导致了这场误会
hence this misunderstanding.
让我把这件事捋清楚
So let me get this straight.
昨晚你闯入了市停尸房
Last night you broke into the city mortuary
然后从波茨的办公室里偷了文件
and stole files from Potts' office.
这其中的误会在哪
Where exactly is the misunderstanding?
我从未偷过东西
I never stole anything.
我看了看文件就把它们放回去了
I looked at the files and put them back.
而且也不是在昨晚 而是昨天下午
And it wasn't last night, it was yesterday afternoon
波茨先生外出吃午餐的时候
when Mr Potts was out for lunch.
我也没有强行闯入
And I didn't break in.
我有钥匙 为什么要强行闯入
Why would I when I have a key?
你复制了市停尸房的钥匙
You duplicated a key for the city mortuary?
我有其他选择吗
What choice do I have?
有人在昨晚闯入了市停尸房 那个人不是我
Someone else broke into the mortuary last night and it wasn't me.
我不会跟你撒谎的 威廉
I wouldn't lie to you, William.
这句话就是赤裸裸的谎言
That's a blatant lie itself.
- 斯嘉丽小姐 - 菲茨罗伊警探
- Miss Scarlet. - Detective Fitzroy.
新发型
New haircut?
很帅气
Very smart.
长官 我有一条信息给你
Sir, I have a message for you.
我应该告诉过你我不在这里 我在休假
I thought I told you I wasn't here. I'm on my day off.
是的 长官 但警司找你
Yes Sir, but the Superintendent has asked for you.
他说事态紧急
He says it's urgent.
别动
Do not move.
威廉
William.
你是相信我的 对吗
You do believe me, don't you?
你被指控的是极其严重的罪行
This is an extremely serious offence that you're accused of.
要证明你的清白非常难
It's going to be damn hard to prove it wasn't you.
进来
Come in!
威灵顿 这位是萨克利先生
Ah, Wellington. This is Mr Thackeray.
早上好 先生
Good morning, sir.
我希望这是个美妙的早晨 督察
I hope it is a good morning, Inspector.
毋庸置疑 这是一个可怕的夜晚
It's been a bloody awful night, that's for sure.
萨克利先生是首席验尸官
Mr Thackeray is the chief coroner.
是非法闯入市停尸间一事吗
The break in at city mortuary?
闯入的不止一间
Break ins.
复数
Plural.
我们刚刚得知
We've just had word that
肯特镇和瑞士屋的停尸房昨晚都被闯入
the mortuaries in Kentish Town and Swiss Cottage were broken into last night.
每间里的机密文件都被盗了
Confidential files stolen from each.
我相信你已经拘留了肇事者
I believe you have the perpetrator in custody.
没错 艾德蒙
We do indeed, Edmond.
那个女人有犯罪前科
That woman has a history of breaking the law.
我的手下跟她打了一次又一次的交道
My man in the city has had to deal with her time and time again,
但这次她太过分了
but this time she's gone too far.
那个女侦探
The lady detective.
真是荒谬
What nonsense.
斯嘉丽小姐跟管理市停尸间服务的职员
So Miss Scarlet has had some minor grievances with the clerk
有着一些小摩擦
who runs the city mortuary service.
在其中一个犯罪现场找到了证据
There was evidence found at one of the crime scenes
那个犯罪现场就是这里
that place is out there.
这肯定会带来一种假设
Surely you are working under the assumption
即闯入了一间停尸间的人也闯入了其他两间
that whoever did one break in must have done the other two.
没错 这是一种假设 长官
Yes, that would be the assumption, sir.
我要立即起诉那个女人
I want that woman charged without delay.
着手在办了
It's all on hand.
位于伦敦北部的女子监狱
把斯嘉丽小姐直接带去霍洛韦
Take Miss Scarlet directly to Holloway.
在进行深入调查时 可以把她关在那里
She can be kept there whilst further investigations are undertaken.
深入调查 有必要吗
Further Investgation? What need is there of that?
你掌握了所需的一切证据 费格斯
You've got all the evidence you need, Fergus.
- 起诉她 - 但是长官...
- Charge her. - But Sir...
这是命令 督察
That's an order, Inspector.
是 长官
Yes, Sir.
抱歉 伊莱莎...
Sorry, Eliza...
她在哪
Where is she?
我也想知道 这样我就能对她大发雷霆了
I wish I knew so I could give her a piece of my mind.
她除了害我担心之外什么也没做
She does nothing but worry the life out of me.
现在她不仅是个逃犯
Not only is she now a fugitive,
还又一次地耍了我
but she's also made a complete fool out of me again.
我和您一样急于找到她
I'm as frantic to find her as you are.
天知道她在哪
God knows where she is.
天知道她正处于什么危险之中
God knows what danger she's in.
不会有我抓住她时那么危险
Well, not as much danger as she'll be when I get my hands on her.
请不要这么说 督察
Please do not talk like that Inspector,
这一点也不绅士
but it's not gentlemanly.
你知道她惹上了多大的麻烦吗
Do you have any idea how much trouble she's in?
那您必须帮帮她
Then you must help her.
我都不知道她在哪 怎么帮她
How can I when I don't know where she is?
有个人可能知道她在哪
There was one person who might know her whereabouts
我们谈话期间 我已经让手下去追捕他了
and I have my men hunting him down as we speak.
如果摩西有一点动静
If Moses so much as sneezes,
我们都会对他穷追不舍
we will be down on him like a ton of bricks.
您为什么认为摩西知道这一切
What makes you think Moses knows anything?
这句话原意是"像贼一样亲密"
他俩亲密无间
Those two are thick as thieves?
如果看到她 或者听到她的消息
If you see her or you hear from her,
立刻派人找我 艾薇
then you send for me Ivy, immediately.
你确定没被人跟踪吗
Are you sure you weren't followed?
你们怎么总这么问我
Why do people always ask me that?
我担心小姐
I'm worried about my girl.
你确定该这么做吗
Are you certain this is the right thing to do?
按计划行事
Just stick to the plan.
我做不到
I don't think I can do it.
你刚刚才骗了督察
You just lied to the Detective Inspector.
你做得到
You can do this.
跑了
Gone.
跑去哪了
Gone where?
我不知道 长官
I don't know sir.
你拘留的头号嫌疑人跑了
So a prime suspect who was in your custody has done a runner.
你还找不到她 一个女人
You're unable to locate her, a woman.
她是个私家侦探 长官
She's a private detective, Sir.
- 她有人脉... - 你不算吗
- She has contacts... - Are you not one of them?
我保证完全没参与 长官
I can assure you that I've had no hand in this, sir.
我还可以保证
I can also assure you
伊莱莎·斯嘉丽不是凶手
that Eliza Scarlet is not the perpetrator.
我们找错方向了
We're barking up the wrong tree.
够了
Enough!
看来我们目前有利益冲突
Now it seems to me we have a conflict of interest here,
我建议你转去调查另一个案子
so I'm going to recommend you'll move to another case.
恕我直言 长官
With all due respect, Sir,
不能这样
that would be a mistake.
首席验尸官很有人脉和影响力
The chief coroner's a man of connection and influence.
我日子会很不好过
so I'm gonna make my life extremely difficult.
宽限我一天 长官
Give me one more day, sir.
我初入这份工作 小子
Now, I have not long been in this job, laddie, and I can assure you
你最好别让我丢了它
you do not want to be the reason I lose it.
宽限批准
You have your day.
找到她
Find her!
是 长官
Yes, Sir.
市停尸房
公众止步
贵客造访 荣幸之至
What a privilege it is to have such a visit.
上次这么荣幸
Not since Prince Albert himself
维多利亚女王的丈夫
还是阿尔伯特王子亲自为我们的
graced us to open our new autopsy wing
新验尸楼揭幕
have I been so honoured.
我也很荣幸 波茨先生
And the honour is all mine, Mr. Potts.
我只是应我丈夫萨克利先生的要求而来
I am merely here at the request of my husband, Mr Thackeray.
他说 "塞西莉亚 你一定要去拜访波特先生
'Cecilia', he said, 'You must pay Mr Potter a visit
看看他经历了这等痛苦后 恢复得怎么样了"
and see is he quite well after such a distressing episode'.
首席验尸官
The notion of the chief coroner
能想到我这样卑微的职员
giving an employee as lowly as myself any thought is...
已经足以慰藉了 萨克利夫人
that's comfort indeed, Mrs Thackeray.
但这次的非法闯入一事 让我觉得被侵犯
But this business with the break-in has left me feeling somewhat violated.
想到有人未经授权
To think someone came into this,
就进入我的私人圣地
my private sanctuary without authorization.
我说"有人"
I say someone,
但我清楚这人是谁 警方也是
but I know exactly who it was and so do the police.
是啊 我都听丈夫说了
Yes, my husband told me all about it.
是个年轻女子吧
Some young woman, was it not?
我听说她是个私家侦探
I hear she's a private investigator.
一个淑女做这个 真少见
What a curious job for a lady.
那女人毫无淑女样子
There's nothing of the lady about that woman.
她到底偷了什么
What exactly was it she stole?
萨克利夫人
I thought you said your husband
我记得您说 您丈夫都跟您说了
told you all about it, Mrs Thackeray?
他确实说了 但...
He did indeed, but..
我有点健忘 你知道女人都这样...
I have quite forgotten. Ah, you know how us ladies are..
一次记不住太多东西
it's hard to retain too much information at any one time.
我不信
I do not believe you.
我很清楚 像您这样的夫人
It is abundantly clear to me that a lady such as yourself
不仅有美貌 还有智慧
possesses great brains as well as beauty.
谬赞了 波茨先生
You're kind, Mr. Potts.
但我确实忘了些细节
But it is nevertheless true that the details have quite faded me.
您介意我们换个话题吗
Would you mind if we did not discuss that woman?
我需要注意血压
I have to be mindful of my blood pressure
想到她我又很苦恼
and she has a habit of causing me great vexation.
喝茶
Tea.
天啊 我都忘了来干什么了
Goodness, I'd quite forgotten the reason for my visit.
我们夫妇想邀请你共进晚餐
My husband and I would like to invite you for dinner.
今晚
This evening.
在首席验尸官家里吗
At the chief coroner's house?
我会努力减少问题
And I will endeavour to keep my questions to a minimum.
不给您徒增苦恼
I'd hate to cause undue vexation.
我... 萨克利夫人 没有的事...
I... Mrs Thackeray, nonsense...
您想知道什么
What is it you wish to know?
三个停尸房的机密文件都被偷了
Confidential files were stolen from all three mortuaries.
包含二十五年前 1857年八月的
They contained lists of unidentified bodies who died 25 years ago
无名尸体清单
in the August of 1857.
还有其他的吗
Anything else taken?
我们得告诉伊莱莎
We should let Eliza know.
还不行
Not yet.
我有更多发现前 她必须低调
She must lie low until I've found out more.
她藏身的安全屋到底在哪里
Where exactly is this safe house she's holed up in?
我希望是个体面的地方
I hope it's respectable.
比不上克拉里奇酒店 但也还行
It's not exactly Claridges, but it will do.
克拉里奇酒店是伦敦最具贵族气质的五星豪华酒店
天啊
Oh my God.
斯嘉丽小姐 欢迎来我的城堡
Miss Scarlet, welcome to my castle.
希望你别见外
I hope you've made yourself home.
好 好的 克莱门汀
Hi, Clementine. Yes, yes.
摩西已经带我熟悉了所有陈设
Moses has shown me all the amenities.
谢谢收留我
Thank you for allowing me to shelter here.
有人给我莫须有的指控
I have allegations made against me that are completely false.
他们一直这样
Aren't they always?
所以这些莫须有的指控是什么
So what are these false allegations?
说我非法闯入市停尸房
It's a break in at the city mortuary
这些说辞都是假的
and for your information the claims are false.
堡区的吗
On Bow Lane?
嗯...
Mm..
我姐姐克莱门汀在那条街工作
My sister Clementine works that street.
你姐姐也叫克莱门汀吗
Your sister's called Clementine, too?
我所有姐妹都是
All my sisters are.
好让妈妈记得谁是谁
Made it easy for our mother to remember who's who...
如果我姐姐的所在街道出事
If something happened on my sister's patch
她应该知道
she'd know about it.
虽然她很吓人
she'd know about it, 'orrible though she is.
但我可以去找她
I could pay her a visit though.
看看她知道什么
See if she knows anything.
那我太感激了
I'd be most grateful.
多感激
How grateful?
毕竟我冒这么大险去见她
I take great risk in going to see her.
上周她一拳打进一个婆娘的脸
Last week she punched a dog in the face.
这个摩西是关键
This Moses is the key.
只有他能带我们找到她
If anyone can lead us to her, it's him.
长官 我拿到你要的消息了
Sir, I've got the information that you asked for.
去吧
Get to it.
- 我说错什么了吗 长官 - 关门 菲茨罗伊
- Did I say something wrong, Sir? - Shut the door, Fitzroy.
我虽然相信斯嘉丽小姐是清白的
Now, I do not believe that Miss Scarlet is guilty in this
但我接到的命令是抓捕她
but my orders are to find her,
而不是找真正的嫌疑人
not to go looking for alternative perpetrators.
所以这个调查只能你知我知
So this line of inquiry is to remain strictly between us.
你有问题吗 警探
You have a problem with that, detective?
不 长官
No, Sir,
我没问题
do not have a problem with that.
很好
Good.
你有什么发现
And what have you got for me?
从三个停尸房偷走的文件
The files stolen from each of the three mortuaries
包含一份1857年八月的无名尸体清单
contain a list of unidentified bodies from August 1857.
废话 说点我不知道的
Yes, yes, tell me something I don't know.
然后我搜查了关联性
Then I searched for a link,
是男是女 相近的年龄
male female, similar ages,
死因
cause of death,
但遗憾的是
but unfortunately those details
那些细节只在墓园中有记录
only exist in records at the cemeteries themselves, but...
我找到了每个墓园的地图
I managed to find maps of each cemetery
和坟墓的位置
and where the graves are located.
都用 X 标记了
I've marked them with an X.
有多少墓园
How many cemeteries are there?
十四个 长官 每座都有个贫民墓
14, Sir, with one pauper grave in each.
要我和您一起去吗 长官
Shall I come with you, Sir?
不用 我需要不动声色
No, I need to do this quietly.
回去值班吧
Go back to your duties.
是 长官
Yes, Sir.
克莱门汀 你去哪里了
Clementine, where have you been?
你出去几个小时了
You been gone for hours.
见过你姐姐了吗
Did you see your sister?
她怎么说
What did she say?
她知道非法闯入的事吗
Does she know anything about the break-in?
看到她了... 气色... 很好...
Saw her... very nice... well..
还行吧...
whatever...
嗯 其实不太好
yeah, it wasn't very good
她和我们祖母比赛摔跤
since the wrestling match with our grandmother.
她看到真小偷了吗
She saw the real thief?
克莱门汀...
Clementine...
克莱门汀
Clementine.
海格特公墓
你们应该感到羞愧
You should be ashamed of yourself.
我要报警
I'm calling the police!
站住
Stop!
我是警察 女士
I'm a police officer, madam.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
就是有点发抖 我丈夫是这里的牧师
Just a little shaken, my husband's the vicar here.
他出任务了
He's away on business.
我只有一个人
I'm all alone.
可怜的
Poor soul.
那些盗墓贼
Those grave robbers,
他们毫无道德
they have no morals.
你知道埋在这里的是谁吗
Do you know who's buried here?
没人知道
No one knows.
贫民墓地
It's a pauper grave.
伦敦大都会警察厅
苏格兰场
我当时在家中客厅里
I was in my parlour in the Vicarage.
我喜欢在那里处理信件
I like to carry out my correspondence there.
你是怎么发现小偷的
So, what alerted you to the robbers?
我正给我姐姐阿加莎写信
I was writing to my sister Agatha,
听到屋外有声响
I heard a noise outside.
今天我们没安排葬礼
We weren't expecting any burials today.
我丈夫外出执行教会工作
My husband's away on church business,
在坎特伯雷和大主教同住
staying with the Archbishop himself in Canterbury.
所以你听到屋外有声响
So you heard a noise outside?
我出门查看了一下 立刻就意识到
I went out to see what it was and instantly I knew.
是偷尸体的
Body snatchers.
他们把尸体卖给医学院赚钱
It's a lucrative trade selling corpses to the medical profession.
给解剖学课提供尸体
They supply bodies for anatomy classes.
就是肢解
Dissections.
嗯 我知道怎么回事
Yes, I am aware of the practice.
我朝他们大喊 让他们停下
I shouted at them to stop.
他们根本没想到牧师家里有人
They was so shocked that someone was at the Vicarage.
他们肯定觉得那是空房子
They must have assumed it empty.
然后他们看见一个男人 就是你
Then they saw you, a man.
督察 要是您当时不在那里
Had you not been there, inspector...
我都不敢想会发生什么
I try to think what might have happened.
你看清他们的相貌了吗
You got a good look at them?
有一个是黑头发 另一个的头发...
One had dark hair and the other was..
浅一点
Fairer?
两个都是中等个子
Average build, the pair.
有伤疤 纹身之类有特点的地方吗
Any scars, tattoos, distinguishing features?
我没看到 但是他们都很邋遢
None that I saw but they were very grubby.
脸上和手上都是灰
Dirt all over their faces, their hands.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
没帮上什么
Haven't been much help.
不 你帮大忙了
No, you've been most helpful.
送埃利斯夫人回家
See Mrs Ellis home.
公爵
Duke.
发现那个牙买加人了
There's been a sighting: the Jamaican.
要把他抓进来吗
Do you want me to bring him in?
不用 他是我的了
No. He's mine.
再来一磅土豆 谢谢 吉姆
And a pound of potatoes, please, Jim.
给您 年轻的夫人
Right you are, young lady.
萨克利夫人
Mrs Thackeray.
真高兴又见到您了
How nice to see you again.
波茨先生
Mr. Potts...
世界真小啊
What a small world?
其实是我母亲就在街角附近
Not really. Mother is just around the corner.
我得去见她一面 告诉她我的好消息
Had to pay her visit to impart my most wonderful news.
什么
Oh?
就是今晚有幸跟您和首席验尸官共进晚餐一事
The honour of dining with yourself and the chief coroner this evening.
我说 母亲 我得为此买条新领带
I said, mother, I might just purchase a new tie for the occasion.
今晚太有幸了
This one's so special.
母亲要是也能来 她一定很开心
Mother would so love to have joined us.
你想的话 就把她带来啊
Well, bring her along if you like.
萨克利夫人 您误会了
Mrs Thackeray, you misunderstand me...
母亲去世了
Mother is dead.
我是去了她的墓地
It is her grave which I visit.
我觉得我必须要
I felt compelled to share
跟她分享这个大喜事
the news of this great honor bestowed upon me.
我真的得走了
Well, I really should be going.
得开始准备晚餐了
Dinner will not prepare itself.
我有些困惑 萨克利夫人
I am more than a little confused, Mrs Thackeray.
像您这样的夫人
It's most unusual that
一般不会亲自来购物
a lady such as yourself does her own shopping.
确实
Indeed,
但是我需要确保
however, I wanted to ensure
今天晚餐的全部食材
that all the ingredients for tonight's dinner
都有最好的质量
were of the highest quality.
我不知道该说什么了
I don't know what to say.
那 今晚见
Until this evening, then.
今晚见
Until this evening.
多好的夫人啊
What a delightful lady.
和她在一起是种幸事 绝对是幸事
It is a treat to be in her company. A treat indeed.
是啊 艾薇是万中无一的
Yeah, Ivy is one in a million.
艾薇
Ivy?
克莱门汀
Clementine,
Clementine.
我刚做了个美梦
I've just had the loveliest dream.
摩西带我去了吉尔伯特群岛 他也太帅了吧
Moses took me to Gilbert, and my God, did he look handsome?
你姐妹克莱门汀怎么说的
What did your sister Clementine say?
哪个 我们有五姊妹呢
Which one - there's five of us?
目击市停尸房入室行窃的那个
The one that witnessed the break-in in the city mortuary.
她说那天夜里下着雨
she said it was raining that night
所以她跑去停尸房附近的拱门躲雨
so she took shelter under the arches near the mortuary.
- 就是在那里看到他的 - 他
- That's when she saw him. - Him?
一个男人
A man.
我知道 他长什么样
Yes, I've gathered that but what did he look like?
最黑的头发 最蓝的眼睛
Blackest of hair, bluest of eyes...
扭曲的微笑 能让魔鬼哭泣
a crooked smile that made the devil whimper.
她认识他吗
Did she recognise him?
跟我猜的一样
It's something I suppose.
男人 黑头发 蓝眼睛
Man, black hair, blue eyes.
你说她当时在躲雨
You said she was sheltering from the rain.
但那晚没下雨
It wasn't raining that night.
事实上 好几个礼拜都没下雨了
In fact, it hasn't rained for weeks,
而且如果很黑的话
and if it was dark,
她是怎么看到他有蓝眼睛的
how did she see he had blue eyes?
她眼神很好
She's got good eyesight.
你说过她只有一个眼睛能看见
You said she had only one working eye.
你根本就没去找你姐姐 对吧
You didn't go and see your sister, did you?
你私吞了我的钱
You drank my money.
她太吓人了
She's terrifying.
我小时候 她偷了我养的小老鼠 拿锅给炖了
When I was a girl, she stole my pet mouse and baked it in a pot.
现在把钱还给我
I want my money back now.
我很乐意跟你聊天 但我得干活去了
I'd love to stay and chat but I've got to get to work.
她在哪
Where is she?
盗墓贼在这里喝酒
Grave robots drink here.
我说 她在哪
I said where is she?
让我进去问一声
Let me go in, ask around,
看看哪两个人是见你就跑的
see about those two who were running from you.
你怎么知道的
How do you know about that?
你一直在跟踪我
You've been following me.
你要进去吗 算了吧
You're going? Forget it.
一里地以外的警察 他们都能察觉到
They will smell police a mile away.
你为什么要帮我
And why would you want to help me?
我们都知道她是无罪的
We both know she's innocent
这帮偷尸体的人才是背后的真凶
and those body snatchers will lead to the real team.
你帮她 我帮你
So I will help you help her.
当然了 得给钱
For a fee, of course.
我不跟犯人共事
I don't work with criminals.
真遗憾 斯嘉丽小姐不像我这么洁身自好
Shame Miss Scarlet doesn't follow my example.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你会来找我的
You're gonna need it.
威士忌
Whiskey.
给你
There you go.
督察
Inspector.
伊莱莎
Eliza.
波茨先生
Mr Potts...
不必麻烦了 伍兹小姐
Do not bother, Miss Woods.
这是你真名吧
It's your real name, is it not?
艾薇·伍兹小姐
Miss Ivy Woods.
是 没错
Yes. Yes it is.
我很抱歉欺骗了你
And I'm so sorry to have deceived you.
但我这么做是有正当理由的
What was for a good reason.
欺骗从没有正当理由的 伍兹小姐
That's never a good reason to deceive, Miss Woods.
我一点都不意外
It comes as no surprise to me
打理这个家的女人想必和她女主人一样
that the lady who runs the house with that woman
会违背基督教义
should herself be unchristian in her ways.
我可以向你保证 我没有撒谎的习惯
I can assure you I don't make a habit of lying.
我爱那个女孩 而且愿意为她付出一切
I love that girl and I do anything to help her.
我就不该相信
I should never have believed that
首席验尸官会考虑邀请我这样的人吃晚餐
the chief coroner would even consider inviting someone like me for dinner.
他该觉得 我终于认清我自己的位置了
He'd think I'd know my place in the world by now.
基督教早期使徒 为人高洁
而且你没有学习巴拿巴
And you haven't learned Barnabas...
我真的非常抱歉 波茨先生
I really am very sorry, Mr Potts.
我之前从没做过这样的事情
I've never done anything like this before.
哈
Hah!
振作 点 伍兹小姐
Take heart, Miss Woods.
因为你已经骗到我了
Because you had me fooled.
再见
Good day.
波茨先生 你真的花钱买领带了吗
Mr Potts, did you spend money on a new tie?
来吧 给钱
Come on, cough up.
赢的这些够我出去找女人的了
I think I'll take a lady out with my winnings.
不如就找
How about...
你妈妈
Your mum?
谁在那
Who's there?
我手头有个活在招人
I'm looking for a man about a job.
能让你们赚大钱的活
The kind that can make you serious money.
生意好做吗
Is business good?
相当好 老兄
Booming, mate.
要是我没被这个忘恩负义的缠住就更好了
Been even better if I weren't stuck with this ingrate.
去你的吧
Get on with you.
带他们去牢房 分开关着
Take them to the cells. Keep them separate.
我先审这个
I'll question this one first.
- 我什么都没干 - 闭嘴
- I've done nothing! - Shut your mouth!
我不喜欢这么粗暴的
I do not like to be manhandled.
我今天最爽的 就是逮捕你
Best part of my day, arresting you.
做戏做全套嘛
We need it to look real.
是你的主意
This was your idea.
我帮完忙了 现在该你了
I got to your team. Now it's your turn.
我要是说 跟你交易是件愉快的事
Well, I'd like to say it was a pleasure doing business with you,
你也知道我在撒谎
but you know I'd be lying.
告诉我斯嘉丽小姐在哪 你会拿到更多
More where that came from, if you tell me where Miss Scarlet is.
我会监视你的
I'll be watching you.
我猜也是 督察大人
I'd expect nothing less, Inspector.
这个斯嘉丽小姐怎么还没入狱
Why is this Miss Scarlet not in prison as we speak?
她绕过了整个大都会警力的追捕吗
How has she evaded the entire Metropolitan Police force?
我知道这样不妙 但请相信我
I know it's not ideal, but trust me.
你都抓到她了
You had this woman here
却让她从你眼皮子底下溜走了
and she slipped through your fingers.
我受够这种胡闹了 费格斯
Well, I've had enough of this nonsense, Fergus.
我要跟你上级汇报
I'm taking this up with your superiors.
埃德蒙
Edmund...
给我让开
Out of my way.
长官 案件有进展
Sir, we have a development in the case.
你抓到那个女人了吗
You have the woman back in custody?
不 长官 是更好的消息
No Sir, I have something better.
确认一下
So just to confirm,
这不是雇你们去海格特盗墓的女人吧
this is not the woman who hired you to rob the grave at Highgate Cemetery?
那个人更老些
She was much older.
这个老一点的女人
And this older woman is the same
你认为闯入三间停尸房行窃的就是她
as who you believe broke into the three burgled mortuaries.
你怎么知道的
How do you know this?
因为你翻来覆去说的这些失窃文件 她那里就有
Because these nicked files that you keep banging on about,
她雇我们把文件提及的每个死者的墓挖一遍
she had them. Paid us to dig up every name on there.
但那些墓都没有名字
When I say name, the graves didn't have any.
都是些贫民墓
All of them pauper graves.
她在找什么
And what was she looking for?
不清楚
Not a bleeding clue.
不管她在找什么
But whatever it was
她能挖到的也只有尸骨
all she found were bags of bones.
那么
So...
描述一下这个女人
Tell me about this woman.
名字 年龄 外貌
Name, age, appearance.
我不知道她的名字
I don't know her name.
只知道别人叫她
Only that they call her
"血腥玛丽"
Bloody Mary.
她坐了很多年牢
Been inside for years.
伦敦关押重罪犯人的监狱
应该是在新门监狱
Newgate, I think.
至于她长什么样
And as for what she looked like,
你应该知道 你见过她
well, you should know - you met her.
什么
What?
那天在海格特公墓 我和沃茨先跑了
When me and Watts did a runner at Highgate
我们以为她完蛋了
we thought she was done for,
那个骚货穿着裙子还怎么逃命 对吧
but the silly tart couldn't run away in a dress, could she?
不对 我只见到了牧师的妻子
No, the only person I met was the vicar's wife,
埃利斯夫人
a Mrs Ellis.
兄弟 那可不是牧师的老婆
That was no vicar's wife, mate.
那是血腥玛丽
That was Bloody Mary.
我可算是明白了
Just so I'm clear, crystal clear,
嫌犯就在那间屋子里 被你放跑了
you had the perpetrator in that very room and you let her go.
长官 万分抱歉
Sir, I can only apolo..
你太让我失望了 小子
This is very disappointing, laddie...
我就该坚信我的直觉
Clearly I should have stuck with first instinct.
我不会再犯这样的错了
I will not make that mistake again.
- 长官... - 另一位警官会接手本案
- Sir... - Another officer will take over the investigation.
长官 我...
Sir, that..
你怎么了
What happened to you?
我去见姐姐了
Went to see my sister.
什么 那是她弄的
What, she did that?
我已经尽可能开高价了 但她好像更生气了
I gave as good as I got. Actually I think she came off worse.
我打听到了点消息
Now, I have some information.
我姐姐的确看到了盗贼
My sister did say the face.
是个女人 浅色头发 黑裙子
It was a woman, fair hair, black dress.
挺老的 至少五十岁
Old, very old, at least 50.
她认出是谁了吗
Did she recognise her?
不清楚
Not a clue.
不像那个在我工作的酒馆喝酒的苏格兰场警察
Unlike the constable from Scotland Yard who drinks at my local.
他嘴里就藏不住秘密
How he loves the chat when he's had a few.
我觉得我也能做女侦探了
Reckon I'd make a good lady detective myself.
把你知道的都告诉我吧
Tell me everything you know.
我正要来接你
I was just coming to get you.
那个克莱门汀有点本事
She's a wily one, that Clementine.
我以后要经常找她办事
Remind me to employ her more often.
你去哪
Where are you going?
去结案
To solve the case.
但你还没有进行调查
But you have not been working the case.
我调查了 我有好消息
I have and I have news.
- 你无罪了 - 我无罪了
- You're in the clear. - I'm in the clear.
来吧 摩西
Come on Moses.
有活干了
We've work to do.
海格特公墓
长官
Sir.
牧师怎么说
What did the vicar say?
不出所料
What I expected.
他没结婚
He has no wife.
我要的情报呢
Where's the information I requested?
鉴于您已经被正式调离此案
Since you are officially off the investigation,
我觉得用脑袋记下来更安全
I thought it safer to memorise it
以免他们不让我出警局
just in case I was stopped coming out of the yard.
别得意忘形了 小子
Don't get carried away, man.
但您确实被调离此案了
But you are off the case, Sir.
我不想聊这个
I don't wish to talk about it.
可是每个人都在聊这个
It's what anyone can talk about.
谢谢他们
Good for them.
现在能不能请你
If you would kindly impart the information
把你小心藏在脑袋里的情报拿出来
that has been so carefully concealed in that brain of yours
快点告诉我
and hurry up about it.
血腥玛丽的真名叫玛丽·道森
This bloody Mary's real name is Mary Dawson.
五十年代 她是某个钻石走私帮的一员
She was part of a gang of diamond smugglers back in the 50s.
她在新门监狱服刑二十五年 上周释放
She served 25 years at Newgate, was released last week.
怎么了 长官
What is it, Sir?
卢卡斯父子花店
法灵顿 希利亚德街
谁会给贫民墓送花
Who sends flowers to a pauper grave?
是的 那座坟墓每月都会收到鲜花
Yes, that particular grave receives flowers each and every month.
把寄花人的地址写给我
Write down the address of the sender for me.
没问题 督察
Certainly, Inspector.
干什么
What?
抱歉 长官 我只是...
Sorry, Sir. It's just...
您之前被调离过案子吗
Have you ever been taken off a case before?
我说得很清楚了 我不想谈这件事
I thought I made it clear that I do not wish to talk about it.
没错 长官 抱歉 长官 明白
You did Sir. Sorry, Sir. Understood.
长官 姑妄言之
For what it's worth, Sir,
门罗长官把您换成了...
the officer Munro replaced you with this...
抱歉 长官 您不想谈这个
Sorry Sir, you do not wish to talk about it.
我谢谢你 警探
Thank you, detective.
换成谁了
Who is it?
- 卡尔迈克 长官 - 卡尔迈克
- Carmichael, Sir. - Carmichael？
那家伙也就会去啤酒厂调查了
Could investigate a booze up in a brewery, that one.
长官 您要的地址
As requested, Sir.
买花人的地址
Address of the account holder.
谢谢
Thank you.
挺奇怪的
It's a curious thing,
今天除了您之外
but you're not the first person who has inquired
还有人打听过这位买家的信息
about that particular account today.
还有谁打听过
Who else has inquired about it?
一位女士 金发 神色坚毅
A lady. Blond hair. Determined to me.
我不知道怎么开口
I don't know where to begin.
我可以解释
I can explain.
不必了
Don't bother.
确保斯嘉丽小姐待在马车里
See to it that Miss Scarlet stays in the carriage.
是 长官
Yes, Sir.
你好 斯嘉丽小姐
Hello, Miss Scarlet.
不要和她交谈 也别让她离开你的视线
Do not converse with her or let her out of your sight.
待会儿跟你算账
I'll deal with you later.
督察
Inspector?
我以为这个案子已经交由别人负责了
I thought you'd been replaced on the investigation.
我也以为您至少会提一下
And I thought sending flowers to a grave listed in the stolen files
给失窃文件里提到的一座坟墓送花的事
might have been something that you would have mentioned.
我和那座坟墓的联系牵扯进此案
No, it's merely a coincidence that my connection with that grave
纯属巧合
should have dovetailed with this investigation.
萨克利先生 我从警多年
I've been in the force a long time, Mr. Thackeray
根据我的经验
and in my experience,
所谓巧合 从来都经不起推敲
a coincidence never holds up to much scrutiny.
那你这次就错了
Well, in this case, you're wrong.
这个解释很简单
It is a simple explanation.
但我并不乐意谈论
However, it's not something I'm comfortable to speak of,
我也没义务跟你解释
nor should I have to explain myself to you.
您要是愿意
Well, if you prefer,
可以跟卡尔迈克警探解释
you can explain yourself to Detective Carmichael,
门罗警司现在派他负责此案
who I believe Superintendent Munro has now assigned to this case.
我可以保证 他不会像我一样孤身前来
And I can assure you he will not be as discrete as I am.
真相是
The fact is...
我出身贫寒
I had a humble upbringing.
不只是贫寒
There's more than humble.
我出身于济贫院
I was born in the workhouse.
我不愿谈及我的出身
It's something I don't like to talk about，
也从不透露
and rarely reveal,
特别是拥有这种地位以后
particularly being a man of such status.
但我从小就立志
But from a young age I was...
一定要出人头地
utterly determined to make something of myself,
你可以看到
and as you can see,
我成功了
I was successful.
这一路上 有很多人帮助过我
There were many people who helped me along the way.
尤其是我妻子
Not least of all, my wife.
我永远感激她
And for that I'm forever grateful.
简言之
So in short,
没有这些贵人 我的人生可能大不一样
my fate could have been somewhat different.
作为基督教徒 以及首席验尸官
And as a Christian man, and in my position as chief coroner
每当我路过一个贫民墓 我都会献花
whenever I happen upon a pauper grave, I like to send flowers.
这是小小的敬意
It is a small kindness
它能帮我铭记
and it helps me remember.
铭记
Remember?
若非上帝开恩
There, but for the grace of God,
我也会沦落至此
Go I.
好了
So.
先生 谢谢您坦诚相告 但是...
Well, I appreciate your candor, Sir, but...
关于此案 我还有一些问题要问
I'm afraid there's still some questions that I need to ask regarding the case.
为什么 还没结束吗
What, why? Surely we're done here?
我说结束才算结束 萨克利先生
We're done when I say we're done, Mr Thackeray.
你们怎么知道我在这儿
How did you know I was here?
威灵顿督察特别嘱咐我
Inspector Wellington specifically ordered me
不要和你说话 斯嘉丽小姐
not to converse with you, Miss Scarlet.
好吧
Very well.
我很惊讶 像你这样有风度的绅士
Although I'm surprised that a gentleman with impeccable manners,
也会这么粗暴
such as yourself, would be so rude,
我只是在执行命令
I'm only following orders.
请原谅 我对你怀有崇高的敬意
Please forgive me, I do hold you in the highest regard.
我不想给你添麻烦 菲茨罗伊警探
I don't wish to get you into trouble, Detective Fitzroy.
但是回答一个简单问题 有什么坏处吗
But answering one simple question, can it really do any harm?
花店老板说
The florist advised that
你问过他 是谁给贫民墓送花的
you'd been asking who sent the flowers to the pauper grave.
但我没和花店老板说过话
But I didn't speak to the florist.
是摩西替我问的
Moses got that information to me.
那花店老板说的金发女人是谁
Well then, who was the blond lady the florist spoke of?
我不认识什么玛丽·道森或者血腥玛丽
No, I do not know this Mary Dawson or Bloody Mary,
管她外号叫什么
or whatever the devil she's called.
我和你一样 急于抓住这个犯人
I'm as anxious as you to get this criminal into custody
查明到底发生了什么
and find out what the hell is going on.
督察 我已经回答了所有问题
And I've answered all your questions, inspector.
我妻子和女仆出去办事 马上回来
My wife and the maid will be back from my errands soon.
我要你在她们回来前离开
I'd like you gone before they return.
您似乎急于赶我走 萨克利先生
You seem extremely keen to get rid of me, Mr. Thackeray.
你的来访可能让我的名声毁于一旦
Well, a reputation can be undone by such a visit.
我不想变成无聊的谈资
I do not want to be the topic of idle gossip.
我以为家里只有您
I thought you were alone.
那是女仆
No, that'll just be the maid.
就是陪您妻子外出办事的那个女仆吗
The maid who's running errands with your wife?
别开门 求你了
No, do not open that door. Please!
很高兴再次见面 督察
Nice to see you again, Inspector.
玛丽 把手枪放下
Put the revolver down, Mary.
我正要和你说同样的话呢
I was about to say the same to you.
如果不照做
And if you don't,
我就一枪崩了萨克利夫人
I will shoot Mrs Thackeray in the head.
玛丽 求你了 不要这样
No, Mary, please, please do not do this.
闭嘴
Shut up.
待会儿再跟你算账
I'll deal with you later.
我说
I said,
把枪放下
put it down.
踢过来
Kick it towards me.
很好
Good.
但转念一想
But on second thoughts,
- 我还是要杀了她 - 不要
- I think I'm gonna kill her anyway. - No!
我建议你别这么做
I would recommend that you do not.
你知道 用警察的武器是一种冒犯
You know that using a policeman's weapon is an offence.
难道你希望我派菲茨罗伊警探来吗
Would you have preferred if I had dispatched Detective Fitzroy?
伦敦大都会警察厅
苏格兰场
我的真名是阿尔菲·弗兰普顿
My real name is Alfie Frampton?
玛丽·道森曾是我未婚妻
Mary Dawson was my fiancee.
我们就是两个小混混
We were small-time crooks
但实施了一次钻石盗窃行动
but we managed to pull off a diamond heist.
我什么时候能见我妻子
When can I see my wife?
她跟此案毫无关系
She knows nothing of any of this.
继续说
Get on with it.
我带着钻石逃走了
I took the diamonds and ran.
但玛丽找到了我 她就像个...
But Mary tracked me down. She's like a..
她是个疯女人
It's a mad woman.
她袭击我 她...
She was attacking me. She was..
想把钻石收入囊中
desperate to get hold of them.
所以我吞下去了
So I swallowed them.
你把钻石吞下去了
You swallowed the diamonds?
她给我留下了这道疤
And there were times she gave me this.
警察收到密报赶来 逮捕了玛丽
The police turned up after a tip-off and arrested Mary.
我侥幸逃脱
But I managed to escape.
既然她进去了
And with her inside.
我看到了解脱之道
I saw a way out.
将她抛在身后
To leave her behind.
将我的过去抛在身后
To leave my past behind.
我伪造了死亡
So I faked my own death.
你用了海格特那个贫民墓里的尸体
You used the corpse from the pauper's grave in Highgate.
所以你每月都会献花
That's why you sent flowers to it each month.
可怜人
Poor soul..
无论他是谁
Whoever he was
他给了我新生
gave me a new life.
弗兰普顿把尸体搬去一个藏身处
Frampton took the body to one of their hideouts,
和那人互换衣物
changed clothes with the man,
然后在他下颌处划了一刀
and then gave him a cut down his cheek,
就像道森对他做的那样
just like Dawson had done to him.
我记得他告诉您
I'm pretty sure he always told you
他那道疤是在克里米亚战争中留下的
that he got that scar from the Crimea, Sir.
我并非唯一相信他的人
I'm not the only one who believed him.
他跟所有人都是这么说的
He told everyone that.
长官 我不是在质疑您的判断
I wasn't questioning your judgment, Sir.
玛丽·道森坐牢时
From her prison cell,
在文件里看到了尸体的事
Mary Dawson read about the body in the papers
她以为那是她未婚夫
and assumed it was that of her fiance.
等她刑满释放
and then when she served her time,
她开始寻找他的坟墓
she went about tracking down his grave.
请进
Come.
菲尔普斯警探 请坐
Detective Phelps come and take a seat.
继续
Continue.
道森相信 她能在那些坟墓里
Dawson believed that she would find the diamonds
找到弗兰普顿吞下去的钻石
that Frampton had swallowed in one of those graves.
但她不知道的是
But what she didn't know
他已经卖掉钻石 重塑自我了
was that he'd sold them to reinvent himself.
他上了医学院
He put himself through medical school,
改变了人生
he changed his whole life.
来点威士忌吗 菲尔普斯警探
Whiskey, detective Phelps?
谢谢您 长官
Thank you, Sir.
你朋友 斯嘉丽小姐 怎么样了
What of your friend, Miss Scarlet?
萨克利一开始希望把脏水泼给她
Thackeray wanted to pin this on her at the earliest opportunity
希望调查就此了结
in the hope that the trail would end there,
如果道森找到了他
and then, if Dawson did find him,
他会和她达成某种协议
and then, if Dawson did find him, then he would cut a deal with her.
我想我已经完全清楚了
Well, I think I'm fully briefed.
就这样吧 威灵顿督察
That will be all, Inspector Wellington.
长官 我知道我违背了命令继续调查...
Sir, I know that I disobeyed orders by continuing with the case...
就这样吧 督察
That will be all, Inspector.
是 长官
Yes, Sir.
菲尔普斯警探
Well, Detective Phelps.
我听说大家对你的评价很不错
I've heard nothing but good reports about you.
深入介绍一下你自己吧
Tell me more about yourself.
我们一直在寻求忠诚之士
We're always on the look out for a good loyal man.
是 长官
Yes, Sir.
谢谢 长官
Thank you, Sir.
男人真幼稚
How childish men are!
他很快就会原谅你的
Still, he'll get over it.
他不会的
No, he won't.
对门罗这样的人而言 忠诚胜于一切
Loyalty is everything to men like Munro,
而我违抗了命令
and I disobeyed an order.
所以是我的错咯
Oh, so this is my fault?
确实是
Actually, yes.
是我救了萨克利夫人的命
I was the one who saved Mrs Thackey's life
可能还救了你的命
and most probably yours, too.
我听说 你和摩西合作了
So I hear you and Moses made quite the partnership.
一个好的开端
First of many.
我只是在取笑你 威廉
I'm just teasing you, William.
但你知道 我不喜欢他
But I don't - you know - I don't like him.
我该回去工作了
Now, I should get back to work.
或许这样比较好
It's probably a good idea,
试着让警司重新认可你
trying to get back into the superintendent's good books.
伊莱莎 你能不能假装一下你说这话是为我好
Eliza, will you at least pretend that you say that for my sake,
而不是为你自己考虑
rather than your own benefit?
威廉 你有时候真的很看不起我
William, you really do have a low opinion of me sometimes.
只是有时候吗
Only sometimes?
今晚有什么计划吗
So any plans for this evening?
本来有
Well, I did have
结果被艾薇搅黄了
till Ivy buggered them up.
噢对 是叫贝茜对吧
Oh yes, Betsy wasn't it?
很抱歉
Sorry about that.
斯嘉丽小姐
Miss Scarlet.
威灵顿督察
Inspector Wellington.
你们慢聊
I'll leave you to it.
波茨先生
Mr Potts,
在你开口前 请让我表达歉意
before you say anything, please let me apologise.
我不是来见你的 斯嘉丽小姐
I'm not here to see you, Miss Scarlet.
波茨先生 你收到我的讯息了
Mr Potts, you received my message.
伍兹小姐 我很高兴来赴约
And I would be delighted to take you up on your offer
品尝你亲手做的布丁
of that homemade steamed pudding, Miss Woods.
阿尔伯特王子的最爱
Prince Albert's favorite,
我还额外加了葡萄干
and I've added some extra raisins.
请进
Come on in.
■
更多精彩 请登录深影论坛 shinybbs.vip
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
■
关注深影字幕组
微信公众号，更
多影视资讯，等
你来发现